[{"answer": "I think Carol had it exactly right when we interrupted what she said.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What do you say then to America as you say, it makes me feel safe?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Alan Dershowitz?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, the picture should have been published.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "What you do about it, Alan Dershowitz?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "All right.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Carol Roth?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Think about some of the greatest and most iconic photographs ever published.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Alan?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "And to mark history.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What benefit did this photo have?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Well, this is the very debate that I'm sure is being had all over America because they had been used, as I say, by almost every other form of media now who are therefore repeating the apparent offense of running the original picture which is hypocritical if you take a view against it.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "What does this photo have any -- have any benefit for?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Because all people care about is getting elected.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Why can't they get around the table and negotiate properly?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I think the morale is set so low right now on both sides.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Well, what do you make of this and what does he make of this?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "And the polls support that.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "And that is a very bad position for the Republicans to find themselves in, isn't it?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I'm just --", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Is that an option?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Yes, just hold on, ma'am.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "My granddaughter?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "It's the worst imitation I've ever heard.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Alan Dershowitz, have you ever heard anything so ludicrous?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "I think it's pretty innocent and gave us all a laugh today so --", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Abby, final word on this?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Well, there have been reports already that Syria has weaponized its sarin, it's a nerve gas, already into Scud missiles, into artillery, and in the bombs.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "Is it actually news in the sense that this is the first we've heard of this or are the Pentagon do you think now briefing this is a reality?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "Well, I suppose we don't know.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "How do we know this intelligence is true?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "He said, no, not yet.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "And what did he say?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "First of all, I just don't think that we're being duped by the administration.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "The question is, twofold, one is Assad likely to do this as one last hurrah, and secondly, what will America actually do if it comes to it?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "It's hard to see how it is possibly advances his cause except as part of a negotiation.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Why would he risk the wrath of the world descending on him over such an action?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "I don't think that happens.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "When do the colonels come after him to use a Latin phrase?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Did he need to do this and what is the fallout going to be here?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "That's the tragedy.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "How are you feeling about it now?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- you know, I think that Hillary Clinton has made a very, very strong statement today.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "What should America be doing that it's not, do you think?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "No, it certainly is.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "It's just absolutely disgusting, isn't it?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "We'll have to check that out.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Is he getting more than me?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "So fantastic.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Is she nice, Taylor Swift?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Well, you know, Piers, good businesses will be checking the supply chain.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "When we talk about these Christmas presents, which obviously there are a lot made in China, in India and other places, that flood into America and to Europe, what responsibility do businesses have that sell these products to try and find out what is going on at the origin or them, in terms of these sweat shops with these young kids?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "India at the moment has no law that bans child labor completely.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "And what pressure should countries, perhaps like America, be putting on countries like India to be dealing with this child labor issue?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "You've got remember, Malala was shot simply because she wanted to go to school.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What can we do about the treatment of young people like her that are being victimized by the Taliban, by other organizations like that, to try to protect them going forward?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "I have no doubt that people are working very hard to get a deal.", "docId": "121205pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "What do you think should be happening here to try and get a deal to avoid the fiscal cliff happening?", "qSentId": 687}]